[
    {
        "question": "Type 0 supervisors are most commonly applied in mainframes",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Paravirtualization does not affect the guest operating system",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Application containment is one of the most efficient virtualization approaches",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Microsoft launched first commercial virtual machines",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The virtualization requirement postulate that virtual machine manager has full control over system resources",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Intel 80 x 86 CPUs were popular base hardware for virtualization purposes in late 1970s",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Host system is protected from a virtual machine, but several virtual machines running on the same host are not protected from each other",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Virtual machine managers allow to make snapshots of host system",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "When a single image of a virtual machine is used as a source for multiple running guests, we call this templating",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Guest virtual machines share information about their interrupts",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "The drawback of privileged instructions lies in",
        "options": [
            "sequential realization",
            "additional time overhead",
            "pointer issues",
            "difficult memory management"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Nested page tables allow for",
        "options": [
            "data corruption protection when creating new guests and their paging systems",
            "up of the virtual machine manager paging",
            "efficient management of page tables for guests and virtual machine manager",
            "managing higher number of guests by virtual machine manager"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which type of virtual machine manager offers purely hardware-based support for virtualization",
        "options": [
            "type 0 hypervisor",
            "type 1 hypervisor",
            "type 2 hypervisor",
            "type 3 hypervisor"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you call a situation, where there are too many virtual machines being created",
        "options": [
            "virtual machine overload",
            "virtual machine overflow",
            "virtual machine sprawl",
            "virtual machine sequencing"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of solution should be recommended for a bank that has updated its hardware architecture, but for stability reasons would like to maintain the old software",
        "options": [
            "application containment",
            "emulation",
            "paravirtualization",
            "type 1 hypervisor"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "In synchronous writes data is being stored in caches, with caller obtaining the control",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "As guests may have multiple addresses, virtual machine manager must work as a virtual router for",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What allows virtual machine manager to re-translate guest pages into real page tables",
        "options": [
            "virtual cache",
            "nested page tables",
            "virtual page tables",
            "linked page tables"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    }
]